翻译：野火春风 hongjie@gmail.com
天!
Whoa!
嗨, 嗨, 嗨!
Hey, hi, hi.
怎么样啊?
How's it hanging?
－ 你们提前回来了.
－ 啊－哈.
￡- You guys are home early.
￡- Uh￡-huh.
发现你们俩在沙发上－－
你们可以想象一下我们有多吃惊
lmagine our surprise
to find you two on the couch￡-￡-
对不起. 我觉得自己好像又回到了高中时代.
Sorry. l feel like
l'm back in high school.
Amy, 好啦.
那是唇印吗, 小姐?
Amy, come on.
ls that a hickey, young lady?
－ 不是, 不是.
－ 耶, 我看到拉.
￡- No, no.
￡- Yeah, l see it.
你妈妈知道你出来和这个--这个无赖约会吗?
Does your mom know you're going
out with this￡-￡- this hoodlum?
求你了, Barone先生,
别告诉我妈妈.
Please, Mr. Barone,
don't tell my mother.
行行行,
我明白了.
All right, okay,
l get it.
我好可怜.
l'm pathetic.
你们在说什么啊?
What are you
talking about?
我是一个和父母生活在一起的成年人
l'm a grown man
who lives with his parents
并且还要接受帮别人照看小孩的工作
这样他才能和他女朋友亲热.
and has to take babysitting jobs
so he can make out with his girlfriend.
－ 不是这样的, Robert.
－ 不.
￡- That's not true, Robert.
￡- No.
－ 还是有点正确的.
－ 噢, 晕.
￡- lt's a little true.
￡- Oh, shh.
Robert.
也许会变得更糟糕.
Could have been worse.
如果让我父母帮忙照看孩子，
而我们这样走进来.
We could have walked in
on Mom and Dad babysitting.
－ 你饿了吗, 亲爱的?
－ 不饿.
￡- You hungry, dear?
￡- No.
－ 我做了薄烤饼.
－ 不吃了, 我上班要迟到了.
￡- l got pancakes.
￡- No, l'm late for work.
－ 我可以带些薄烤饼走吗?
－ 可以, 等一下.
￡- Can l get them to go?
￡- Yeah, give me a second.
嗯, 开饭了! Frank
OKay, let's go, Frank!
－ 厨房并不是整天都开放的.
－ 不象你的嘴巴.
￡- Kitchen isn't open all day.
￡- Unlike your mouth.
嗨, 昨天晚上整晚的喧哗是怎么回事啊?
Hey, what was with all
that racket last night?
什么喧哗?
What racket?
大概在9点的样子,
我听到你的女朋友在说话.
Like around 9:00,
l heard your girlfriend talking.
Amy说话就是喧哗?
Amy talking is racket?
她又不是和我说话,
那好, 就算喧哗吧.
She's not talking to me,
so, yeah, racket.
那么就是说我不能再和别人说话了?
So l'm not allowed
to talk to people any more?
你当然能说话啦,
亲爱的.
Of course you are,
dear.
顺便说一句,我同意Amy说的那句话.
By the way, l agree with
what Amy was saying.
你并不可怜.
You are not
pathetic.
你是在监视我?
You were spying on us?
我只是刚好听到.
l was passing
an air vent.
你真聪明, 大仙.
You're so cute, Yogi.
她叫你大仙.
She calls you Yogi.
你下巴上有果汁.
You got some syrup
on your chin.
你有没有叫她波波?
Do you call her Boo Boo?
－ 我来帮你弄掉.
－ 别, 别这样, 妈妈.
￡- Let me get it.
￡- No, stop it, Mom.
－ 别瞎搞了.
－ 别，你别擦了.
￡- Stop fiddling.
￡- No, you stop it.
－ 好了, 别闹了!
－ 行, 就这样吧. 我要搬出去住了.
￡- No, you stop!
￡- Okay, that's it. l'm moving out.
搬出去住?
真荒唐.
Moving out?
That's ridiculous.
你打算怎么走?
What are you
gonna do?
在棍子上系上波尔卡小点的手帕
Tie a little polka dot hanky
around a stick
然后跳上货运列车?
and hop
a freight train?
我有车.
l have a car.
妈，你别笑了.
You can stop
laughing now, Ma.
行动吧.
行动吧, 伙计.
Do it.
Do it, man. Go.
你别吵吵了.
Robby在这里过的幸福着呢.
You be quiet.
Robby's very happy here.
你和你妈妈住在一起,
亲爱的, 你会过得很好.
You stay with your mother,
honey, you'll be fine.
－ 他哪也不会去.
－ 哦，我会的.
￡- He's not going anywhere.
￡- Oh yes l am.
别犯傻了.
Don't be silly.
我们来想想上次的事情
Let's remember
what happened the last time
上次你也象这样耍花样.
you pulled a stunt like this.
妈，我要结婚了.
行了吧?
l got married, Ma.
Okay?
我要帮出去
是因为我要结婚了.
l moved out
'cause l got married.
对啊,
你要结婚了.
That's right,
you got married.
然后?
那有怎么样?
And?
What happened with that?
你会在那糟糕的女人身上花掉所有的钱
You lost all your money
to that awful woman
那女人会抹上三种不同眼影.
with the three
different eyeshadows.
我说Joanie会拥有一辆很不错的守车(载货火车最后一节).
l will say that Joanie
had a nice caboose.
Joanne, 爸.
她的名字是Joanne, 明白吗?
Joanne, Dad.
Her name was Joanne, all right?
都一样, 这辆火车将不会靠站.
Either way, that train's not pulling
back into station.
关键问题是,
你会过得很悲惨.
The point is,
you were miserable.
我们欢迎你回到这里来
And we welcomed you back
into this house
而且我们会再次让你得到心灵满足.
and we made you
whole again.
－ 记住这些了吗?
－ 嗯.
￡- Remember that?
￡- Yeah.
那现在你还想搬出去自己一个人过吗?
And now you want to go
out on your own again?
那不正是最明智的选择吗?
ls that really
the smartest thing?
那好.
疯狂的想法被摆平了.
Good.
Craziness settled.
欢迎回来,
Welcome back,
大仙.
Yogi.
我们应该给你准备个野餐篮子.
We should get you
a picnic basket.
听好, 兄弟, 你的想法是对的.
你是应该搬出去住了.
Listen, man, you're right.
You got to move out.
－ 我是准备从这里搬出去住.
－ 什么时候?
￡- l am gonna move outta here.
￡- When?
我准备好的时候.
When l'm ready.
好. 呆在这儿.
听天由命吧.
Fine. Stay here.
Do what you want.
嗯, 我会去做我想做的任何事情的?
非常感谢.
Oh, l can do whatever l want?
Thank you very much.
我和你说过多少次了让你搬出去住了?
How many times
have l told you to move out?
你总是能找到些站不住脚的借口.
You always got
some lame excuse.
－ "我正为钱发愁呢."
－ 钱是个很好的借口.
￡- "l'm worried about money."
￡- Money is a good excuse.
"我还只有33岁."
"l'm only 33."
"他们让我在门上装个锁."
"我还只有37岁."
"They let me put a lock on the door."
"l'm only 37."
你知道吗?
你不需要任何借口了.
Yeah, you know what?
You don't need any more excuses.
－ 我不会再让你帮出去了n.
－ 很好. 很棒.
￡- l'm not gonna tell you to move again.
￡- Good. Great.
好.
你余生都这样过着悲惨的生活吧
That's right.
Stay miserable for the rest of your life
并且在犹豫是不是应该搬出去,
但是现在已经是太晚了
and wonder if you should've
moved out, but now it's too late
因为你已经老了，顶也秃了，
并且还和爸爸妈妈生活在一起.
'cause you're old and bald
and living with Mom and Dad.
最终你会发现
And you're gonna
find out
对棒球来说，指定击球员并不好.
that the designated hitter
is bad for baseball.
九名队员击球, 九名队员接球,
这就是游戏规则.
Nine guys hit, nine guys field,
that's the game.
棒球就是按照这样的规则进行比赛的的.
lt's the way it was meant
to be played.
哎，你会愿意和爸妈搬家到佛罗里达去
What, are you gonna move
to Florida with Mom and Dad
然后住在退休村庄里?
and stay
at a retirement village?
我不会飞上1500英里
l'm not flying
1 ,500 miles
去看你穿着短袜，拖着着凉鞋的.
to see you wearing
socks with sandals.
Ray,你怎么总是烦我?
Why are you
bothering me, Ray?
因为你总是抱怨和他们生活在一起,
Because you're always complaining
about living with them,
但是, 喂, 看看现在谁还在这里.
but hey, look
who's still here.
行了, 够了.
你怎么不去忙你自己的事情啊?
All right, enough.
Would you mind your own business?
我只是恨你像现在这样生活, 因为－－
l just hate seeing you
like this, 'cause￡-￡-
无论怎么说,
我和你一样.
whatever,
l like you.
等等, Raymond.
妈, 请坐下.
Wait, Raymond.
Ma, sit down, please.
我有些话要和你说.
我要搬出去住了.
l've got something to tell you.
l'm moving out.
－ Robby, 够了, 我已经听烦了－－
－ 妈, 妈.
￡- Robby, enough, l'm tired with￡-￡-
￡- Ma, Ma.
我感谢你为我做过的一切.
l appreciate everything
you've done for me.
食物...
For food...
饮料－－
for beverages￡-￡-
行了, 行了.
Okay, okay.
－ 坐下来吧, 我给你做些吃的.
－ 不用了, 妈.
￡- Sit, l'll make you something else.
￡- No, Ma.
我已经下定决心了.
My mind's made up.
谢谢你,
Raymond.
Thank you,
噢, 不用谢我.
Oh, don't thank me.
－ 谢谢你.
－ 嗯.
￡- Thank you.
￡- Hmm.
为什么他要谢你?
Why is he thanking you?
我把他的外套拿回来了.
l brought back
the jacket for him.
－ 已经不早了.
－ Raymond!
￡- lt's late.
￡- Raymond!
我非常激动，我从来没有象今天这样激动过.
l am so psyched. l have never been
psyched like this in my life.
－ 嗨, Ray, 我发自内心地－－
－ 行了, 走吧!
￡- Hey, Ray, from the bottom of my￡-￡-
￡- Okay, go away now!
别激动, 别激动.
Easy, easy.
我要走了,
l'm walking
out of here,
优雅地，慢慢地
nice and slow
行不?
Okay?
我们以后再谈这件事,
We'll talk
about this later,
当你能够再次眨眼以后.
when you start
blinking again.
－ 把他拦下.
－ 喂!
￡- Stop him.
￡- Hey!
－ 他干了什么?
－ 让我走!
￡- What did he do?
￡- Let go of me!
别跑.
这只会让事情更糟.
Don't try to run.
it only makes it worse.
为什么你老是来搅和我们家的事情?
Why did you stick
your nose into our affairs?
－ 谁给了你这权力的?
－ 你怎么敢的!
￡- Who gave you the right?
￡- How dare you!
Robby是我留下的最后一件东西.
现在他就要离开我们了，都是因为你.
Robby's the last thing l have left.
Now he's leaving because of you.
－ 哎, 我只是想－－
－ 噢, 你只是想!
￡- Look, l just thought￡-￡-
￡- Oh, you just thought!
你有没有考虑过我呢?
Did you think
about me?
你有没有曾经考虑过我呢?
Do you ever
think about me?
对, 考虑过吗?
Well, do you?
你考虑过吗?
Do you?
我－－ 我不会忘记这件事的, Raymond.
l￡-￡- l'm not gonna
forget this, Raymond.
－ 妈.
－ 我也不会.
￡- Mom.
￡- Me neither.
你? 你总是对他大喊大叫，说他应该搬出去住,
You? You're always yelling at him
that he should move out,
让他感觉自己很失败.
making him feel
like a loser.
我并不是真想让他搬出去.
l don't really
want him to go.
如果他走了...
lf he goes...
就只剩下我和她了.
it's just me and her.
& 我将脱离控制了，我－－ &
& l'm about to lose
control and l￡-￡- &
－ 喂, 爸.
－ 别走啊!
￡- Hey there, Pop.
￡- Don't go!
我爱你.
l love you.
喂，兄弟', 如果有什么我能帮你的,
Hey bro', if there's anything
l can ever do for you,
你尽管告诉我，行么?
you just let me
know, all right?
& 我就要脱离控制了，我想我会喜欢. &
& l'm about to lose control
and l think l like it. &
你能不能别唱了!
You could stop singing!
想想好的一面吧,
On the bright side,
现在你们可以买吊扇了.
now you can buy
a ceiling fan.
嗨, 依人小鸟.
Hey, Snugglepants.
哦, 今天可是不一般.
Oh man, what a day.
我今天采访Ewing, 你知道的,
l had this interview
with Ewing, you know,
他迟到了三个小时，我不得不等他.
and he was three hours late
and l had to wait for him.
噢，我累了，亲爱的.
Oh l am tired,
sweetness.
噢 耶, 噢.
Oh yeah, oh.
噢，亲爱的,
感觉真不错.
Oh baby,
does that feel good.
来.
Come here.
－ 你在干什么?
－ 帮你放松啊.
￡- What are you doing?
￡- Trying to help you relax.
哦 老天, 现在又开始做梦了.
Oh God, now the dreams
are gonna start again.
别犯傻了.
Don't be silly.
我当成做梦，
是希望你别再对我发疯了.
l take it this means
you're not mad at me anymore.
我不会对你发疯的.
l can't stay mad at you.
你去看过Robby的新家吗?
Have you been
to Robby's new place?
没有，他要一个星期时间来安置下来.
No, he wants a week there
to get settled.
好的, 如果你去的话,
帮我拍张照回来.
Well, when you do go,
take a picture for me.
我想他不会邀请我去的.
l don't think
l'll ever get invited.
妈, 你应该为他感到高兴啊.
Ma, you should
be happy for him.
他感觉很好.
他感觉自己独立了.
He feels good.
He feels independent.
进来吧, 小家伙们.
Come on, guys.
－ 哦! 宝贝们好.
－ 奶奶好.
￡- Oh! Hi, sweetheart.
￡- Hi, Grandma.
来，宝贝.
Hey, guys, hey.
嗨, Deb, 猜猜发生什么了.
看看谁原谅我了.
Hey, Deb, guess what.
Look who forgave me.
哦 很好啊.
Oh good.
因为在我们生活中总会有困难的.
'Cause there was such a hole
in our lives.
Robby离开我的最大好处
The only good thing
about Robby leaving me
是我能有更多的时间来陪你们大家.
is l get to spend more time
with all of you.
干衣机好了.
That's the dryer.
Debra, 我发现你买了一些新的内衣了.
Debra, l noticed some new underwear
in there for you.
要比一般的要暴露一些.
A little more revealing
than usual.
把Robert 弄回来吧.
Get Robert back.
否则
就剩下我们和她了.
Otherwise
it's just us and her.
你愿意在这里出现不好的感觉吗?
Are you starting
to get a bad feeling here?
我刚刚就开始有那种感觉了.
l'm just starting
to get feeling back.
请进!
Coming!
你好. 我一定是地址弄错了.
Hi. l must have
the wrong address.
我找Robert Barone.
l'm looking
for Robert Barone.
是这里. Robby 上周租了我们车库楼上的房间.
Yes. Robby rented the room
above our garage last week.
－ 车库上面?
－ 是的.
￡- Above the garage?
￡- Yes.
我是他的弟弟 Ray.
l'm his brother Ray.
噢, Raymond!
请进.
Oh, Raymond!
Come right in.
我叫Rita Stipe. 我刚想叫Robert下来呢.
l'm Rita Stipe. l was just about ready
to call Robert down.
Robby!
吃饭了!
Dinner!
－ 来了!
－ 这个男孩不错.
￡- Coming!
￡- He's such a nice boy.
Harry!
下来吧!
Get down here!
我不会再帮你热一次的!
l'm not heating
this stuff up for you!
－ 饿了吗, 亲爱的?
－ 不用了, 我妻子正在做饭－－
￡- Are you hungry, dear?
￡- No, my wife's making￡-￡-
你就坐在那里吧.
You sit yourself
right down there.
我们有抹在土豆上的酸奶油什么的吗?
We got sour cream
for the potato or what?
就在你面前.
lt's right
in front of you.
－ 是我喜欢的那种吗?
－ 不是, 我买的是你不喜欢的那种.
￡- That the kind l like?
￡- No, l buy the kind you don't like.
这位是谁啊?
Who's this guy?
－ 他是Robby的兄弟.
－ 嗯, 你好.
￡- This is Robby's brother.
￡- Yeah, hi.
－ 我们有培根(烟熏火腿肉)块吗?
－ 你眼睛瞎了?
￡- We got the Baco Bits?
￡- Are you blind?
如果这是一条蛇,
它就已经咬着你了.
lf this was a snake,
it would have bit you.
如果它是一条蛇的话,
我宁愿吃它，而不去吃那炖肉.
lf it was a snake,
l'd eat it instead of that pot roast.
嗨, Raymond.
你来这里有什么事情吗?
Hey, Raymond.
What are you doing here?
我刚好路过，想来看看地方.
l just came by
and wanted to see the place.
我就猜到你应该是第一个来看我这里的
l guess you should be
the first to see it
因为你就是我来到这里的原因.
since you're
the reason l'm here.
我跟你说,
我会带你到处看看
l'll tell you what,
l'll show you around
在我一吃完这闻起来最美味的晚餐以后.
right after l eat what smells
like the best dinner ever.
坐, 坐, 坐.
Sit, sit, sit.
－ 这些都是你最喜欢吃的肉.
－ 哈!
￡- lt's all your favorite meats.
￡- Ah!
嗯, Rob...
So, Rob...
－ 过得怎么样?
－ 很好.
￡- how's it going?
￡- Good.
虽然我独立生活，总是有些不可思议.
lt's kind of weird
being on my own, though.
独立生活, 嗯.
那么, 嗯...
On your own, yeah.
So, uh...
这地方会不会让你想起某个地方?
does this place
remind you of anywhere?
有个当警官的兄弟，是不是感觉很棒, Raymond?
lsn't it great to have a brother
who's a police officer, Raymond?
我觉得他在身边让我感觉安全多了.
l know l feel much safer
knowing he's around.
被人欣赏感觉总是不错的.
lt's nice
to be appreciated.
或者被人注意.
Or noticed.
Raymond?
Barone?
不会是 "Newsday"的Ray Barone吧?
Not "Newsday"'s
Ray Barone?
－ 是的, 那就是我.
－ 好棒的家伙.
￡- Yeah, that's me.
￡- Holy crud.
我们家来了个名人了.
We got a celebrity
in our midst.
－ Harry Stipe.
－ 耶, 你好.
￡- Harry Stipe.
￡- Yeah, hi.
真让人激动啊.
一个作家.
How exciting.
A writer.
我喜欢你写的任何东西.
你怎么没有和我说过你的兄弟是谁呢?
l love everything you write. How come
you didn't tell me who your brother was?
一定是忘记了.
Must have
slipped my mind.
那么, 给"Newsday"写文章感觉如何?
So, what's it like
to write for "Newsday"?
还好,
我想.
lt's okay,
l guess.
一个一流的作家.
A big-time writer.
而且这么谦虚.
And he's humble.
Robert, 给Raymond留点吃的.
Robert, leave some
for Raymond.
嗯, 我们到了.
Well, here we are.
嗨, 看看这里.
Hey, look at this.
是的, 对这里我还要做些整理,
Yeah, l've got a little more work
to do on the place,
但是，毕竟我搬家了，对吧?
but hey, at least l made
the move, right?
是的.
Yeah.
Shamsky 喜欢这里.
看看他.
Shamsky loves it.
Just look at him.
对的,它看起来再高兴不过了.
Yeah, he's never
looked happier.
小伙子们, 我要去店里买冰激凌了.
Boys, l'm going to the store
for ice cream.
你们要吃点吗?
Do you want some?
啊!
Aw!
谢谢你,  S女士.
Thank you, Mrs. S.
她很特别, 是吗?
She's one
of a kind, huh?
是的, 没有人能够像她那样.
Yeah, no one else
like her.
听着.
Listen.
Robert, 我不认为－－
Robert, l don't think￡-￡-
－ 这是怎么回事?
－ 车库门开了.
￡- What the hell is that?
￡- Garage door opening.
吓坏你了, 哈?
Scared you, huh?
我要告诉你，第一次的时候Shamsky 把我的席子弄脏了.
l got to tell you, the first time
it went up Shamsky ruined my sheets.
嗨, Rob, 我想－－
我想－－
Okay, Rob, l think￡-￡-
l think￡-￡-
下楼回家吧.
Going back down.
我想你应该从这里搬走.
l think you ought
to get the hell outta here.
不, 我已经习惯了.
我甚至都听不见这些声音了.
Naw, l'm used to it.
l don't even hear it anymore.
不是说这个!
你看, Robert,
Not that!
Look, Robert,
这里和家里并没有两样.
this place is no different
than home.
你在说什么?
What are you
talking about?
这里是完全不一样的.
lt's totally different.
我现在住在车库上面,
l'm above a garage,
我在这里有个浴室,
l have a bathroom here,
我可以吃小点心－－
l'm allowed
to bring snacks￡-￡-
来点Fiddle-Riddle?
Fiddle Faddle?
这里的人,
Stipe夫妇,
Those people,
the Stipes,
如果你在其中一位上化更浓的妆，另一位体重加上30磅,
you put more make up on one
and 30 lbs. on the other,
那就是咱爸咱妈了.
that's Mom and Dad.
行了, Raymond,
他们根本就不象咱爸妈.
Come on, Raymond,
they're nothing like Mom and Dad.
他们是犹太人.
They're Jewish.
Amy认为这里怎样?
What does Amy
think of this place?
哎, S女士.
不喜欢我
Well, Mrs. S.
doesn't like me
带女孩子上门.
having visitors
of the female persuasion.
她有点对我看管的太紧了.
She kind of looks out
for me a little too much.
S先生, 他不太喜欢说话,
And Mr. S., he doesn't
like a lot of talking,
除了他们吵架的时候.
except when
they're fighting.
他们就不停地吵啊吵啊吵啊
And then they go on
and on and on
我的天哪!
and oh my God!
也许这不是我预想的重大生活改变.
Maybe this isn't the radical change
l had planned.
不，也有变化啊.
你现在要支付房租了.
No, there's a change.
You get to pay rent now.
傻瓜 白痴 蠢猪!
Stupid idiot moron!
不是, 你不是.
你不是.
No, you're not.
You're not.
不, 你看, 也许我们做些事情.
No, look, maybe there's
something we can do.
也许你可以...
Maybe you can...
搬回家住.
move back home.
对自己好一点吧.
Yeah, make it easy
on yourself.
你看, 你已经表明了自己的想法了.
Look, you've made
your point here.
另外, 假如你搬回家里住，
你知道谁会最开心? 妈妈.
Besides, you know who'd be really happy
if you moved back home? Mom.
那样不是更好吗?
为我们大家?
Wouldn't that be nice?
For all of us?
那将是－－
Robert的家, 可以吃到sloppy Joes三明治.
That would￡-￡-
Robert's home, sloppy Joes.
你说得对,
我不能再呆在这里了.
You're right,
l can't stay here.
耶, 来吧,
我们来, 哈－－
Yeah, come on,
let's, uh￡-￡-
我们来打包吧.
我们回家吧.
let's pack.
Let's get you home.
－ 噢不, 我不能回家.
－ 你的意思是?
￡- Oh no, l'm not going home.
￡- What do you mean?
我要找一个真正属于我的地方.
l'm finding
a real place.
属于我自己的,
没有长辈监管的地方.
On my own,
no adult supervision.
那妈妈怎么办?
我是说, 她非常伤心，并且...
What about Mom?
l mean, she's all sad and...
经常光顾我家.
over at my house a lot.
这些年来我呆在那里，我认识到
All those years l stayed
there l convinced myself
我并没有浪费我的生活，因为那是计划的一部分.
that l wasn't wasting my life
because it was part of a plan.
呆在家里，存些钱，认识个女孩,
Stay at home,
save some money, meet a girl,
然后搬出去，然后你知道的，开始一种生活.
then move out and,
you know, have a life.
结婚, 买房子,
生些孩子,
Get married, buy a house,
have some kids,
变得－－
become￡-￡-
你知道的,
就那些把.
you know,
have it all.
是的.
Yeah.
如果我回去, 我不得不承认我的计划就是泡影了.
lf l go back now, l have to admit
that my plan was nothing.
你必须得找个你自己的地方.
You have to find
your own place.
妈妈让你抓狂了吧, 是不?
So Mom's driving
you crazy, huh?
太恐怖了.
lt's horrible.
我现在怎么办?
What am l gonna
do now?
你要从那里搬走.
You got to get
outta there.
－ Ray!
－ 嗨.
￡- Ray!
￡- Hey.
－ 你看到Robert了吗?
－ 你看了Robert住的地方了吗?
￡- Did you see Robert?
￡- Did you see Robby's place?
是的, 他要从那里搬走了.
Yeah, he's moving
out of there.
－ 我知道你办得到的.
－ Robby就要回家啦.
￡- l knew you could do it.
￡- Robby's coming home.
－ 我要走了，去把他的房间打扫干净.
－ 不用了, 妈妈.
￡- l've got to go and clean his room.
￡- No, Mom.
－ 他要搬到别的地方去.
－ 你去干什么了?
￡- He's moving somewhere else.
￡- What did you do?
是啊, 你去干什么了?
Yeah, what did you do?
你是哪位尊神啊? 凭什么到我家把Robert带走了?
Who are you to come into our house
and take away that Robert?
我跟你说句话,
一流作家先生.
Let me tell you something,
Mr. Big￡-Shot￡-Writer.
我那里需要Robert.
l needed Robert there.
没有他,
家里就只有我和她了.
Without him,
it's just me and her.
那间房子
现在还可以租么?
That room
still available?
翻译：野火春风 校对：野火春风
hongjie@gmail.com QQ:3234721